Bro, we need to make a different tool.
And we can do it.
We can do it.
The one we just described,
we can't just put it here.
We need to put it in a different place.
Then we can take it and see it.
And when it's finalized, we can put it here.
We can see it.
Or we can just put it here.
We don't need a new interface.
We don't need two interfaces.
We can just put it here.
And we can suggest it right-right.
Suppose it's right here.
1 Lakh.
You just did 1.25 Lakh, right?
Or it's okay.
They have searched it.
How does it work in Google Flights?
Prices for this flight is
low at this moment.
Yes.
Have you seen it in Google Flights?
The list of flights is written here.
These prices are high
for this time.
They are unlikely to go down.
Yes, it's written like this.
What do we think about it?
We think it's okay.
We don't get scammed.
Yes.
It's written here.
It's good.
Do you want to sit or do you want to work?
Yes.
It's definitely a
competitive advantage.
Yes.
There are three tips here.
Before the search,
we observed that
your income is
not more than 20,000.
20,000?
First,
the most important
top three tips.
Not yet,
but if you want more money,
these are the three main tips.
If you fix them, it makes a difference.
They are self-employed.
If you get a six-month salary
for half the price of
we can save half of your salary.
Yes.
The rates of the banks are different.
That's why we have two options.
You are a great self-employed person.
I don't know
about Google Flight.
When they say prices are
low, I feel like
I am being fooled.
When they say prices are
low, I feel
this is the right price.
And when they say prices are
high,
unlikely to get low,
forget it.
Yesterday, I got a message from
Cove Air Bufa company.
They sent me
a juicer.
They said, this is our sale.
This is the price of the juicer.
They said, in a year,
no matter how healthy you are,
we will double the difference.
I don't have that much confidence.
What Amazon does is
in every sale,
they hype up
prices before the sale.
Then they give a fake discount.
I never knew
that this price
is the lowest for a year.
So, I go to this sale
and get the next sale
in two months.
Then they say, the biggest sale of the year.
Then they give me a lower price.
Then I get a
bigger sale.
I never knew
that this was the case.
I get trapped in their scam.
I had already told you
about the juicer.
I would have stopped there
for the sale.
Because it is
not about the sale. It is about
making a fool out of the customer.
Even in a sale,
they fluctuate the prices
of the same product.
It is a profit
for them.
But they say,
if the sale of Prime Day is so low,
you will never get the same
sales for the whole year.
So, I will genuinely
stop for Prime Day and spend as much as I can.
The company told me
that if the sale is so low,
they will make a difference.
So, I will plan for the whole year
to spend the money on Prime Day.
But their sales go up
in the whole year.
I will take the biggest sale
So, I don't believe
in their sales.
This is the intelligence
that is being codified here.
This is where
the sections will be made.
First and foremost, the biggest saving.
Combine your and your wife's income
and give your wife
the name of the property.
Give her the certificate of going home.
And get her fan card
printed here.
You can read it in one go.
This is how it is.
We have one side of the road.
We have a good
product to it.
We still have a long way to go.
Now, we have an application.
I will tell you how to do it.
It is not just comparing
our lives.
We are lawyers for you.
How to squeeze the bank.
It is possible.
Actually,
making a feature
is a one-day job.
Because it is
completely AI driven.
We have to say that these are
the customer's parameters.
And you look at all the offers.
And you say that
in minimum efforts, which best offer
will fit the customer?
Making a feature is not
an option. It is mainly design thinking.
Product management.
Engineering is
after thought. Engineering is not
a problem. Product is the problem.
By the way, going forward,
there is no need to
do CTO.
Engineering is
separate, vertical.
It is gone.
Product is vertical.
It is just printed.
What is the need of product management?
This is fine.
I think this is fine.
Let them do what they want.
And here only, we have implemented
three things.
Then they will not feel that
they are getting what they want.
Let them see how much they get.
In the score of
720 to 780,
this will be the best offer.
You don't just sit and watch.
Let them see how much they get.
What do you get from a user?
I mean,
that is exactly how
I would try to use it.
I mean,
first fill the form.
You tell me.
You don't know anything.
Give me the best.